它会扯破衣服
Wow! That ripped!
还扯得很好
That ripped real nice!
你要我说几次  要侧身滑出来
How many times do I have to tell you! You, turn and sliiiide!
侧身滑出来
Turn and slide.
你不是侧身滑出来
You don't turn and slide
而是把它扔出去
You throw it out!
我讨厌每次穿着西装打破伤风针
I'm tired of having to get a tetanus shot every time I get dressed!
不能扔掉  这是我亲手钉的
We're not throwing it out. i built it with my own hands!
好 那卖掉怎样
How about we sell it?
好吧
All right.
好吧  不过你得告诉它们
All right. But, you're gonna have to tell them.
帮你们搬个家介意吗
Do you mind if we stick you in another cabinet?
看来它们没意见
They seem all right with it!
莫妮卡 我是奇普
Hey Monica, it's Chip.
谁是奇普
Who's Chip?
很高兴今天遇见你
Good runnin' into you at the bank today,
我的电话是5559323
so ah, here's my number, 555-9323.
奇普就是奇普马修斯
Chip, is Chip Matthews.
瑞秋的高中舞会舞伴  他打给你干什么
The guy who took Rachel to the prom? Why is he calling you?
我在银行遇见他 他还是好帅
Cause I ran into him at the bank, he is still soo cute.
你好幸运  他是全校最红的男生
Monica You're so lucky! he's like the most popular guy in school!
我知道
I know!
奇普 我是莫妮卡
Chip? Hi! It's Monica.
好  再见
Okay, good-bye.
天  我们聊得好愉快
Oh my God, we just had the best conversation!!
我正要走
I was just leaving.
很好
Good.
我要看报告
Cause I've got a product report to read,
有八页  但愿我不会睡着
it's like eight pages, I hope I don't fall asleep.
为什么 你写的
Why? Did you write it?
你看看
Wow! Look at that
奇普马修斯打电话来  不晓得有什么事
Chip matthews called. i wonder what he wants.
其实
Well ah, actually...
他一定感应到
I bet he sensed that I was ready
我可以跟别的男人上床了
to have sex witive another guy.
那你何不打给他
Well, umm, why don't you give him a call?
-你真的想听  -真的
-Are you sure you wanna hear this? -i'm sure.
奇普 我是瑞秋
Chip! Hi, it's Rachel.
瑞秋·格林
Rachel Green.
你留言给我
Yeah, umm, you left me a message.
你有  我的室友记下来了
Yes you did, my roommate wrote it down.
莫妮卡·盖勒
Monica Geller.
是 没错
Oh, that's right!
他是要约莫妮卡
He called to ask out Monica!
真是尴尬
That-that's gotta be embarrassing!
蠢妞喝醉了
Dumb drunken bitch
谢谢
Thank you!
请问一下
Here's a question.
密西西比以东  最好的橡木家具在哪里
Where'd you get the "finest oak east of the mississippi"?
你先说全国最漂亮的蕾丝在哪里
First tell us where you got the prettiest lace in the land.
这是你们的广告
I'm reading your ad.
不错  是吧
Looks good, uh?
高级视听娱乐柜  精致
Stunning entertainment center.
精致意大利手工
Fine, fine Italian craftsmanship.
天哪  你们要卖娱乐柜
Oh my God, you guys are selling the entertainment center?
为什么  我喜欢那个柜子
Why? I love that thing.
-你们要  -不要
-you want it? -no.
名家手艺
Gepetto?
定价5千
Five thousand dollars?
你疯了
Are you insane?
登广告就要300
The ad alone cost $300.
我要改成50元或再议
I'm changing it to $50 or your best offer.
那有什么利润可言
What kind of profit is that?
你也算是会计师
And you call yourself an accountant.
我不是
Nooo.
那你是什么
Oh. What do you do?
你居然不知道我干哪一行
I can't believe you don't know what I do for a living!
我也不知道
Yeah, I actually don't know...Good,
看有只小猫
Oh, my god, no! shoo, kitty!
看看你
Come on, you!
小疯子
Crazy!
-天啊  -怎么
-oh, my god! -what?
没什么
Nothing.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我只是有一股强烈的感觉
I just have this really strong
这只猫是我妈
feeling that this cat is my Mother.
莫陶克那个妈妈   她是一只猫
You mean the mom you met in Montauk. She was a cat?!
不 她是一位女士
No, no-no, she was a human lady.
这是莉莉妈妈的灵魂
This is the spirit of my mom,
自杀的那个
the one who killed herself.
是她变成一只猫
Are you sure she's in the cat,
还是你又偷吃外婆的青光眼药
or have you been taking your grandma's glycoma medicine again?
没有  疑心病博士
No Dr. Skeptismo!
我很肯定   第一  我有这个感觉
I'm sure. First of all, okay, there's the feeling.
还有  她跑进我的吉他盒里
Okay, and for another, how about the fact that
它的衬里是橘色的
...which is lined with orange felt.
我妈最喜欢的鱼是橘棘鲷
My mother's favorite fish was orange roughy.
猫喜欢吃鱼
Cats like fish.
妈妈
Hi, mommy!
我17年没看到这个笑容了
I haven't seen this smile in 17 years.
-菲比的妈有两颗好大的  -算了
-phoebe's mom's got a huge pair of -let it go!
你什么时候要告诉我  你要跟奇普约会
When were you going to tell me that you're dating chip?
现在吧
Now?
我跟他约会没关系吧
Can i go out with him?
当然有关系
Nooo! It's not okay!
不敢相信在他那样对我之后你会去找他
I can't believe you would want to after what he did to me!
你是说舞会的事
What, that little thing at the prom?
莫妮卡  我2个小时找不到他
Monica! I couldn't find him for two hours!
他跑去跟艾美威许做爱
He was having sex with Amy Welch!
那是高中的事  你怎么还会在意
Come on, that was back in high school! how can it still bother you?
你为什么偏要跟奇普约会
I mean why, of all people would you want to go out with Chip?!
我们的高中不一样
Look, you and I went to different high schools...
少来  我们上的是同一所高中
Okay, that doesn't help me, We went to the same school.
你在高中是风云人物
You went to one where you were popular
你坐奇普的摩托车 穿他的特优选手外套
You rode on chip's motorcycle and wore his letterman jacket.
我穿的是特制的乐队制服
I went to one where i wore a band
那是特制的
They had to have that specially made?!
竟然特别订制的
They had that specially made?
那是家政课的作业之一
It was a home ec project.
天哪   他们说那是给吉祥物穿的
Oh my God, they told us that was for the mascot!
那时候我以为  我永远
Back then, I thought that I would never,
不可能跟奇普约会
ever get the chance to go out with a Chip Matthews,
现在他打来约我
and now he's-he's called me up and asked me out.
我心中那个胖女孩真的很想去  是我欠她的
And the fat girl inside of me really wants to go. I own her this
我从不让她尽情的吃
I never let her eat.
-你去吧  -真的
-you go out with him. -really?
如果可以
Yeah. Just, if it's possible,
你能不能丢下他
could you leave him somewhere
去跟别人做爱
and go have sex with another guy?
我试试看
I'll try.
你们娱乐柜卖得怎样
So you guys having any any luck getting rid of the entertainment center?
昨晚有几通询问电话
Well, there were a couple of calls last night,
但我都觉得不可行
but ah, I don't think any of them are gonna work out.
乔伊有一套严格的筛选过程
Yes, Joey has a very careful screening process.
并非每个人都适合拥有木制品
Apparently, not everyone is qualified to own wood and nails.
别挣扎了
Stop it!
她一直想跑走   跟活着一样
She keeps trying to get away. just like when she was alive.
菲比  你妈要跟我们在一起多久
So Pheebs, how long is your mom gonna be with us?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
可能直到  她能接受我有了
I guess until she gets used to the fact that there's...
新妈妈
...a new mom.
她会很担心自己被取代
Now she's worried that she'll be replaced.
才不会  对不对
Well, that's not gonna happen is it? Noo.
我去房里回个电话
Okay, I have to return a call in the other room.
怎么不在这里打
Why can't you use the phone in here?
我要回个电话给住在海边的妈妈
Well, I'm returning a call from a certain mom at the B-E-A-C-H.
我竟然拼错了
I just spelled the wrong word.
是 我疯了  还是
So, guys, am I crazy, or
有人也觉得   菲比的妈像一只猫
does Phoebe's mom remind anyone else of a cat?
罗斯 别提了
Ross, don't start.
拜托 你们真的相信
Come on, you-you can't tell me you actually believe
那只猫是一个女人变的
that-that there's a woman inside that cat!
我相信
I believe it.
你才不信
No, you don't.
我信
Yes, i do.
你才不信
No, you
知道吗
You know what?
我不会跟你争辩
You're not gonna suck me into this.
你会  你总是要说服别人
Oh sure I am, because you always have to be right.
我才没有好不好  好吧
I do not always have to be--okay, okay.
侏罗纪公园是有可能的
Jurassic Park could happen.
还不赖
Wow! That's ah, that's pretty nice!
Pretty nice?
原谅我的室友  他简直想娶它过门
You'll have to pardon my roommate, he wanted to marry this.
我们没有50块钱 但是你们愿意交换
We don't have 50 bucks, but would you be willing to trade for it?
一艘独木舟吗
We got a canoe.
你知道 我们不需要独木舟
You'know, I, I really don't think we need a canoe.
你们一定要收下独木舟
You gotta take the canoe!
你们把柜子搬走
Just take the entertainment center.
等你们到家 再把独木舟扔掉
Then when you get home, throw the canoe away.
想都别想 那是我亲手造的
We're not throwing it away. i built it.
干得好
Good for you!
你们不会想到
You guys, you're never gonna believe
我在电线杆上发现什么
what I just found tacked up on a telephone pole!
眼熟不
Look familiar?
显然菲比的母亲也叫胡立欧
Apparently Phoebe's mother also goes by the name Julio.
不一样吧  有个小女孩
You guys, there's a little girl in Soho
在找这只猫  知道这代表什么
looking for this cat. I mean, you know what that means?!
知道  五个人平分2百元赏金
Yeah! $200 reward split five ways!
我们要告诉她不
Do we have to tell her?
-当然要告诉她  -但她现在好开心
-yes, we do. -but it's made her so happy.
想念猫咪的小女孩
Little girl misses her cat.
觉得猫是母亲转世的疯婆子
Crazy lady thinks her mother is in a cat.
好了 我要去跟我儿子吃饭
Okay, y'know what, I have to go have dinner with my son,
你们见到菲比会告诉她
can I trust that when you see Phoebe, you will tell her.
谢谢
Thank you.
我最讨厌罗斯是对的
I hate when Ross is right!
他说得对 对吧
He is right, isn't he?
搞不好这一次他错了
Y'know what, I think this might be one of the times he's wrong.
-是吗  -不  他说的对
-you think? -oh, no. he's right.
菲比  关于你的母亲
Uh, Pheebs, about your mom...
你们处得好吗
How's that going?
棒极了 我们一起睡午觉
So great. Oh, we took a nap today
妈在我肚子上睡着还打呼
and my Mom fell asleep on my tummy and purred.
真温馨
That's so sweet.
我去点咖啡
I'm gonna get some coffee.
乔伊你说什么  我马上过去
Huh? What'd ya say Joe? I'll be right there.
-菲比  -我觉得好
-Pheebs... -I just feel so....
知道了   马上来
All right!!I'm coming already!!Jeez!
还没
Not yet, not yet, not yet!
-奇普  -瑞秋  你好吗
-hello, chip. -how you doing?
很好
I'm great!
我有一份好工作 一群好朋友
Got great job at Bloomingdale's, have wonderful friends,
虽然现在没有男朋友
and even though I'm not seeing anyone right now,
却对自己很满意
I've really never felt better about myself.
莫妮卡准备好了没
So ah, Monica ready yet?
她马上就好
She'll be out in a second.
艾美威许怎么样
So, chip, how's amy welsh?
艾美威许  我们自从
Amy Welch? Wow! I haven't seen her since...
莫妮卡快好了
So, Monica about ready?
买这个柜子就对了
This is the unit for you.
坚固耐用  容量超大
Sturdy construction, tons of storage.
都塞得进一个大人了
Some big enough to fit a grown man.
-什么  -对  我就试过一次
-what? -yeah, i got in there myself once.
我的室友赌5元说我进不去
My roommate bet me five bucks that I couldn't,
然后在门把上塞棍子把我关住
and then he stuck a board through the handles that locked me in.
起先很好玩 后来感觉像棺材
Yeah. It was funny 'til I started feeling like I was in a coffin.
你才进不去 它又不够深
No, you, you can't fit in that thing. That's not deep enough.
是吗
Oh yeah? If I can't,
要是我进不去
If i can't...
就少算你5块钱
...i'll knock $5 off the price.
就这么说定
All right, you have yourself a deal.
中文字幕
See? i told you.
有时我会这样的玩
Sometimes I get in here just to get away from it!
有5分钱
Hey, a nickel!
到了
Here we are.
天哪  你的奇车还在
You still have the chipper!
什么
The what?
那是你车子在高中的外号
That's what we called your motorcycle in high school.
摩托车也叫奇车
A motorcycle's a chopper.
你叫奇普
And you're chip.
没事
Never mind.
真可爱
I think it's cute.
奇普亲亲
Wow! A lipper from Chipper.
你还有跟哪些同学联络
So you still in touch with anyone from high school?
有瑞秋 还有
Umm. Well, there's Rachel,
就这样  你呢
and umm, I think that's it. How bout you?
我还在跟西门斯 萨纳混
Oh yeah, I still hang with Simmons and Zana, y'know.
也常跟史宾 莱文 凯利见面
I see Spindler a lot. Devane, Kelly
三不五时会遇见高第
I run into goldie time and
史迪 布朗  苏卡夫 麦奎尔
Steve Brown, brown, sulkov, mcguire...
杰弟 毕斯利
...j.t., beardsley.
就这样
Is that all?
毕了业都会失去联络
Ehh, y'know after high school, you just kinda lose touch.
我有遇见李察多夫曼
Oh yeah! I ran into Richard Dorfman.
-他好吗  -不太好 被我和西门斯敲竹杠
-how is he? -Not so good, Simmons and I gave him a wedgie.
他不是建筑师吗
Isn't he an architect?
建筑师也要穿内裤
Yeah, they still wear underwear.
天哪
Oh, my god!
什么
What?
你还好吧
Are you all right?
怎么了
What happened?
他答应不拿沙发椅的
Awww, man! He promised he wouldn't take the chairs!!
你怎么会被关进去  我们的东西呢
What the hell happened?!! How were you locked in?!! And where the hell is all of our stuff?!!
有一个人来看柜子
Well, this guy came by to look at the unit
他说它塞不下一个大人
and-and he said he didn't think big enough to fit a grown man!
所以你自愿进去
So--You got in voluntarily?!
我是想把柜子卖出去
I was tryin' to make a sale!!
要是让我碰上他  你猜我怎么着
Oh, man, if I ever run into that guy again, do you know what I'm gonna do?
屈服
Bend over?
萨纳干脆让另一个破掉
...and then Zana, just let one rip!!
我不是不喜欢  回忆高中往事
Look, not that I enjoy talking about people who I went to high school with
因为我喜欢
...because i do.
但我们可以聊点别的
but umm, maybe we could talk about something else?
像你  我还不晓得你的工作
Like you, I don't even know where you work?
-你知道的  -我知道吗
-You know where I work! -i do?
电影院 你以前常来
The movie theatre, you used to come in all the time.
你还在影城做事
You still work at the multiplex?
我怎么可能换工作
Oh, like I'd give up that job!
随时都有免费爆米花和糖果可吃
Free popcorn and candy, anytime I want.
我还可以帮你拿海报
I can get you free posters for your room.
谢谢 不用了
Thanks, i'm set.
你还住在家里
Do you still live with your parents?
是 不过我没有门禁
Oh yeah, but I can stay out as late as I want.
他们还真是大搬家  电视 沙发椅
Wow! They really got you guys. Your T.V. The chairs.
微波炉  音响
Oh yeah, your microwave. The stereo.
天哪 他把黑桃5拿走了
Aww, man, he took the five of spades!!
没 在这里
Oh, no-no-no, here it is!
天  怎么了
Oh my God! What happened?
乔伊出生  28年后 我被抢了
Oh, umm, Joey was born, and then 28 years later, I was robbed!!
约会怎么样
So, how was your date?
我高中时一直想跟奇普约会
Well, y'know how I always wanted to go out with Chip Matthews in high school?
今晚我真的跟高中的奇普约会了
Tonight, i actually went out with chip in high school.
真可惜
Honey, i'm sorry.
没关系 我不但跟奇普约了会
Not only did i get to go out with chip...
还甩了他
...i got to dump chip.
-太棒了  -我知道
-that's so great! -I know.
保险公司怎么说
Hey! So ah, what did the insurance company say?
他们说 你们没投保  别再打来了
Oh, they said uh, You don't have insurance here, so stop calling us.
你们没有告诉她
You didn't tell her?!
好
Okay, fine.
听我说
Listen...
这只猫是一个小女孩的
...this cat belongs to a little girl.
路上帖满了寻猫启事
There are flyers all over the place.
对不起
I'm sorry, sweetie.
我们可以陪你把猫送回去
We can take her back with you if you want.
但是她选择来找我
Ohh. Um-hmm. But y'know, she choose to find me.
我得尊重她的决定  对吧
I mean, I have to respect her decision. Right?
-有道理  -说得好
-that's a good call. -that's right.
不对  别闹了
Enough is enough.
我很遗撼你跟新妈妈在一起
Look, I am sorry that you feel guilty or whatever
会有罪恶感
spending time with your new mom,
但这不是你的旧妈妈
But this isn't your old mom.
这是一只猫
This is a cat.
叫胡立欧
Julio the cat.
不是妈妈 是猫
Not mom! cat.
罗斯  你失去过几个父母
Ross, how many parents have you lost?
没有
None.
那你就无法体会
Okay, then you don't know what it feels like
其中一个回来的感觉  对吧
when one of them comes back. Do you?
我相信这是我的母亲
I believe this is my Mother.
就算不是又怎样
Even if i'm wrong, who cares?
你就当个好朋友  支持我
Just be a friend, okay? be supportive.
对不起
I'm sorry.
好的
Okay.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
你可以向
You could.... say
她的妈妈道歉
you're sorry to her mom.
我想她会接受
I think she would like that.
过来
Come here. here, come here.
布非太太
Mrs. buffay?
我为我说的话道歉
Sorry, about what I said,
我实在很伤人
umm, it was, it was insensitive
说你只是一只猫
of me to say that you were just a cat.
显然的  你也是
When clearly you are also
我朋友的母亲
the reincarnated spirit,
的灵魂转世
...of my friend's mother.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们都原谅你
We both forgive you.
那个小女孩怎么办
So honey, what are you gonna do about the little girl?
听我说
Listen.
妈  你对我还是很重要
Mom, I hope you know you still mean a lot to me.
随时都可以回来
You're welcome to come back anytime.
要是她可以变成一张沙发  感激不尽
If she'd come back as a couch, we'd really appreciate it.
走吧 我带你回家
Come on, Mom, I'll take you home.
-我跟你去  -我也去
-i'll go with you. -me too.
我有多的蒲团
I got an extra futon.
你拽个屁  我们这儿什么都没有
Dude, you don't have to brag! We got nothing here!!